Dennis Heit

Philadelphia, PA 19148 mheit602@gmail.com 6102338340

Hello, I am a 23 year old who is currently looking for a job in the software engineering field. I'm a very passionate individual who's experienced in many areas. I am currently enrolled in a coding bootcamp though the University of Central Florida. I have completed many web applications from HTML with CSS to node.js that includes mongoDB and SQL databases. I'm someone who will do everything to be better than I was the day before. You can view many of my applications on my web portfolio, https://mitchellheitsportfolio.netlify.app/ . Thank you for your time, have a good day

Work Experience

Auto Body Technician

MOPPERT BROTHERS AUTO COLLISION SPECIALISTS INC-Morton, PA January 2024 to March 2024

Starting at moppert brothers was good. I completed many tasks that other could not complete. During my time here I, took vehicles apart assessed the damage, wrote up an estimate and ordered parts. I worked on many vehicles at this location from Hondas to Porsches. My work mainly consisted of big collision jobs that included frame swaps, whole body tear downs, replacing windows, finding leaks and many other big jobs.

Auto Body Technician

Karosserie-Wayne, PA September 2020 to October 2023

I am a technician at a auto body repair shop. I have completed many big jobs and made them look better then factory standards with the build when they are finished. This includes hanging sheet metal and getting all gaps even and flush. I have completely disassembled many interiors in multiple car manufacturers. I have completed suspension work and sub-frame jobs. I have ordered parts through the company for the cars that were being worked on and did the inventory on those parts. I Also have completed many high-end jobs such as, Bentleys, Ferraris, Porsches, McLaren, Aston Martin, ECT.

Auto Body Technician

Premier Collision-Chester, PA May 2020 to September 2020

Assembly and disassembly of vehicle to greater spec of factory. This includes full disassembly of vehicles to frame and installing all parts and sheet metal back on vehicle. Parts inventory.

Deli Clerk

BJ's Wholesale Club-Springfield, PA July 2019 to April 2020

During my time working as a deli clerk in bjs wholesale club it was nice. Many of the people whom shop there were regulars and it was very nice to see them come back and ask for me. I had started out in the deli then was pulled back and fourth from the deli to the meat department to cut and package meat items. During my time there I was very professional with all customers that came in to get anything even if it was just a question I assisted the customer as best as I could. If I could not assist the customer I then got someone who was more knowledgeable about the situation so the customer was not stranded.

Education

High school diploma

Sun Valley High School - Aston, PA September 2015 to June 2019

Skills

- Brake repair (6 years)
- Door hanging (5 years)
- Vehicle maintenance (6 years)
- Power tools (10+ years)
- Shocks & struts (5 years)
- Suspension (5 years)
- Automotive diagnostics (5 years)
- Software engineer (1 year)
- Sales (2 years)
- Git (1 year)
- GitHub (1 year)
- JavaScript (1 year)
- CSS (1 year)
- Node.js (1 year)
- MySQL (1 year)
- MongoDB (1 year)
- React (1 year)
- Svg (1 year)
- Bootstrap (1 year)
- JSON (1 year)
- REST (1 year)
- JQuery (1 year)
- APIs (1 year)
- Jest (1 year)

Languages

• English - Fluent

Certifications and Licenses

Driver's License

Additional Information

Took many business classes in high school that included, accounting and personal finance. Those courses went hand in hand with the intro to calculus and honers statistics classes that I was enrolled in. Currently enrolled in a web developer program for the university of central Florida.